What about clients that are close to 3
million LinkedIn impressions in just 90
days? And better yet, they booked 72
sales calls in the third month alone
with no cold outreach. So, in this
video, I'm going to be showing you the
exact five key content formats that we
use that are currently working on
LinkedIn right now to generate not just
reach, but also revenue. And I'm doing
this because after 3 million dollars in
client results and successfully
implementing this for over 50 B2B
companies now, we've collected more data
in these last few months than most
people would in years. [music] So, today
we're going to be pulling back the
curtain on exactly how we achieved these
results and how you can replicate them,
too. All right, guys. So, as you can see
here, we have the screenshot of the
analytics where we literally got them
2.8 million impressions in 90 days
pretty much from zero. Okay? So, these
are absolutely absurd results and not
only that, when I asked them in Slack
how many total calls they booked, we
checked and it ended up being over 72
calls like tracked in Slack, individual
notifications that are directly come
from LinkedIn. Okay? So, this is insane
and you can literally use this if you're
stuck around 200 or less impressions per
post. You can use this if you want a B2B
audience and you don't just want a
bigger one, but you actually care about
quality, right? And you care about
attracting decision-makers who are
eventually going to buy your service.
Number three is if you're still running
2023 era LinkedIn tactics. So, if I see
people, you know, posting polls or
doing, you know, super fancy carousels
which don't really work as well anymore.
And number four is simply just going to
be if maybe you already have the
audience, right? I've spoken to people
who have 50,000 followers and they're
generating less than 5K a month from
their LinkedIn. All right, that is
completely horrible. We are aiming from
anywhere from like two to $10 per
follower. It really varies upon the
niche, but you can imagine, you know,
one of my clients, he has 50,000
LinkedIn followers and he's generated
multi-multi six figures in the last year
from LinkedIn. So, something like that
is like a pretty good ratio, and that's
not even thinking about any of the other
benefits that come with having a
personal brand, right? So, what this
breakdown is going to cover is five
things. We're going to cover five
content formats. So, the exact type of
post that you need to use if you want to
get reach on LinkedIn right now. Number
two is going to be the posting
structure. So, what is the correct
cadence and consistency and strategy
that you should use to train the
algorithm to push your posts to the same
people every single day. Number three is
the weekly content mix. So, how do we
balance out these different types of
posts that we're doing to make sure that
we keep the ICP concentration high, and
we're actually maximizing for trust
building, right? Because if you only
posted personal stories every day,
you're only ever going to have top of
funnel audience. Nobody's ever going to
trust you enough to buy a service from
you, right? Sorry if I'm talking fast,
but I'm really, really into this, and I
am ready to give you guys all of the
value. So, number four is going to be
the lead capture layer. So, lead
capturing is extremely important.
Content isn't the only thing, but it's
also what happens after, right? So, how
can we turn these comments into
connections and into actual pipeline?
Then we have the results. Quick thing,
if you still have not generated leads
from LinkedIn yet, and you honestly just
want to skip this whole testing phase
and not put any of the time to do it
yourselves and just pay some experts to
do it, right? Then there is going to be
a link in the description where we will
essentially just show you what we run
for our clients, and you can apply to
work with us, okay? And we'll see if
it's a good fit. So, if you want to do
that, the link is in the description. I
don't want to waste you guys' time. I
know what you're here for. Let's get
into the value. So, format number one is
the lead magnet post. Now, just to just
to preview you guys a little bit about
the types of results. This is a
screenshot I took of a post we did for
them. We got them 270,000
impressions and 2.7 thousand comments on
one singular lead magnet alone. Nowadays
on LinkedIn, to get these types of
numbers, it's extremely rare, okay? It's
extremely rare. Here are the key parts
of a good lead magnet post. Number one,
we need a core offer. So, the way you
should be thinking about your lead
magnets is you should pick one main pain
point, right, that you solve, and you
need to consider your free resource that
you are giving away to be that bridge to
sort of solve that pain point, right? At
at least as fully as it can, right? And
I would recommend, right now, Claude
prompts  Claude skills are really
amazing.
And that being said, I know that they
can feel a little cheap, and especially
if you're selling an AI-related service,
it can just maybe not make a lot of
sense, in which case you might want to
do something like a more in-depth Notion
document, you might want to do a video
masterclass like this.
Um there's a bunch of different options.
The idea is you just need to make the
resource as easy to consume and as easy
to get value from as possible. Okay? And
obviously, with a Claude prompt, they
can copy-paste that into Claude and
instantly get an output, so that's why
people tend to opt in for those. And as
you can see with this one, this one was
a Claude system, we're basically talking
about using Claude schedule to replace
outreach agencies. We're basically
talking about using Claude schedule to
replace SDRs, because it would basically
like automate scripting and this and
this. So, this sort of pain point was
the fact that all the time that it takes
to like set up outbound campaigns, and
you can see that it really did resonate.
So, the hook structure, I would
recommend starting with a bold claim.
Now, bold claims can be a controversial
take. It could be a client result. It
could be anything, really. Like, for
example, in this case, we said, "RIP
outreach agencies and SDR teams," right?
We decided to be polarizing on purpose.
Obviously, these companies are not going
to die, but it's about polarization, and
it's about getting people talking in the
comments. Now, if you prefer not to do
that, you could simply say, "Hey, look,
this AI system does what these people do
for
this much money, and this AI system's,
you know, free, or it costs $20 a month,
right, for the plan." So, like, you can
find softer ways of talking about it,
but the idea is we need something which
stops the scroll. So, some sort of bold
claim, right? A lot of the time, you
could also just say a result, right? So,
if you have a client result or an
expected result, you can always do that,
right? So, for example, I took a client
from zero to 89K a month in 6 months.
So, I posted a case study about it that
got 900 comments, I think, and the first
line was just like, "This person went
from zero to 89K a month using LinkedIn,
right?"
Anybody that sees that, that's in a
similar situation to them, and wants to
get to the same dream outcome, is going
to be instantly curious. And the fact
that you can't explain, right? You can't
explain it in in two lines. So, they
need to click see more to kind of fix
that to kind of close the open loop,
right? That's the key thing with hooks,
is creating some sort of curiosity and
some sort of open loop where to close
the open loop, they need to click on see
more. And what you'll find with lead
magnets is because we're sending
resources to people in the comments,
that's another open loop. So, they need
the resource to close the second open
loop of actually getting all the value
from it, right? So, it's just like
that's why they perform so well.
Positioning, um I would recommend either
framing it as exclusive internal
material or something where it's like,
you know, other people would usually
charge you thousands for this, right?
Very simple, but adding a line like that
can easily help boost the performance.
Um having a CTA, so with the CTA, you
want to tell people to comment
something. I would say under six letters
is good, just because it's low friction.
One thing I would keep in mind is
nowadays LinkedIn is kind of battling
people who tell you, like, must who say
must be connected in their posts, and
who kind of make it seem like an
engagement farm.
Um so, I would try and avoid that. I
would try and make it just a comment.
And if you want them to connect with
you, you can say that in the image, but
don't say it in the post because it will
suppress reach. Same thing with putting
links, like just don't put links. It
doesn't make sense. Um, because the
whole point with lead magnets is to get
people to comment and then create like
this network effect spiral where it just
goes more and more viral. So, with the
algorithmic engine is exactly what I
talked about. So, when one person
comments, it gets pushed out to all of
their connections. So, it's like a huge
network effect. And then with the
network growth side, because for people
to receive the resource, they do need to
connect with you, which is what you'd
mention in the image or you'd like
subtly mention it in the post. That
means that then people automatically
follow you. Like that's just the way
LinkedIn works. If you're connected, you
follow them. So, you get all these
people which will then see your future
content as well, and they've already
gotten value from you. So, it's an
extremely valuable type of content where
you can extract tons out of the
audience. Now, the top trend as I
mentioned before is AI lead magnets,
okay? Claude skills, Claude prompts. I
would recommend being extremely active
on X specifically so that you can stay
up-to-date with all of the latest
updates, all of the latest models. That
is the best way for you to trend jack
and be the first to those trends.
>> Quick pause. So, if you are an agency
owner or a B2B SaaS founder that is
looking to turn LinkedIn into an inbound
lead generation channel, then I have two
options for you just depending on where
you are at. Option number one is if you
simply want to learn more about our
system and what I've already broken
down, then there will be a one-hour full
course for you to watch after you finish
this video and it will just show you
exactly how we book our clients
consistently 50 to 100 plus calls every
single month. That being said, if you
are past the stage of wanting to learn
it yourself and you want to skip that
whole testing phase and have someone run
it for you, you can apply to work with
us with the calendar link in the
description. On that call, we basically
just see if you're a good fit and how we
usually work with our clients, we'll
show you the whole process. So, if that
is of interest, the next steps are in
the description. But that being said,
let's get back to the video. Format two
is the big name tag post. So, you want
to tag a specific one-on-one company or
figure in your niche directly and link
it to your offering. So, what I would
recommend, and the reason I'm saying
this, is when you tag them, you either
like break down their strategy, right?
Or you roast their strategy, or you talk
about what they're doing so well and
maybe what you'd do in their situation.
Like you Or it's a story about that
company and then you link it to your
service, right? But the idea is just
having a big name to link to in the hook
because that is what people will
recognize and that will then allow you
to associate your brand with them. So,
for example, I made a tweet, right? I
did it on Twitter, but it's the same
concept. I made a tweet about Clay's
LinkedIn strategy. You know what? I'll
just put it up right now. So, I made a
tweet about Clay's LinkedIn strategy.
I made two, actually. And you can see
this one got 190k,
uh where I basically said, "Pay
attention to what Clay's doing on
LinkedIn right now because this is the
most underrated GTM playbook I've ever
seen." So, I'm not saying that I'm doing
anything for Clay, but I'm able to use
their authority and it also pushes my
agenda, which is the fact that LinkedIn
is the best platform and because I truly
believe that. But it's basically the
proof is in the pudding, right? If that
makes sense. Like I'm showing real
examples that back up my point with
these extremely large companies that
people know, and this actually got me
some of the most qualified leads I've
ever gotten simply because the people
which look up to those larger companies
are other larger companies, right? Okay?
So, that's why it performed so well and
that's why I'd recommend that. And on
LinkedIn, it's the same thing, but you
would tag them and ideally hope to get
them to comment so that it gets pushed
out to their audience. So, I did that
with Laura Costa as well recently. She's
an influencer, she has like 300,000
followers. I did that, I got like 200
likes on a normal post with no call to
action. Now, as I said before, there's
an authority transfer. If you simply
talk about a authoritative brand in your
space, you will also be associated with
it. It's that simple, right? Unless
you're like completely roasting them. Um
the content requirement is to try and
make it as accurate as possible. The
worst thing you can do is break down
somebody else's strategy and have it be
completely wrong. Like that's the worst
thing. So, make sure it's all correct.
Don't just use AI to do it. You need to
make sure all of the numbers and like
the strategy is real. Now, an example
would be tagging a billion-dollar
company to analyze their lead gen
approach or tag a company which is
already doing successful lead gen and
explaining it and then maybe explain a
couple things they could do on top of
it, right? Format three is the
proprietary insight post. So, this is a
value post, right? But the thing is, if
you just said, "Hey, here's five tips to
grow your agency." Nobody's going to
listen to that, right? No Nobody cares.
But if I said, "I've spoken to a
thousand plus agency owners and we
manage 50 plus agency agency as clients.
These are the five tips from speaking to
all these people. If you want to grow
your agency as fast as possible in the
next 90 days." All of a sudden, my
authority is so high, like you you can't
bear not to listen to me, right? But the
idea is your value can be the exact
same, but simply because one is backed
by data and experience that is unique to
you or difficult to achieve, it
automatically makes your post way, way
more receptive to the ICP. So, an
example would be, "We have built a
LinkedIn content strategy for over 100
B2B founders. Here is the pattern nobody
talks about." And I would honestly say
making this even more specific because
anyone can kind of say they've spoken to
100 B2B to be
So, making it more specific with
specific results and time frames. So,
saying like, in the last month, right?
Just things which make it as
easy for the prospect to see in their
mind as possible.
Now, the other thing you could do is
save drivers. So, the thing is, if you
have specific metrics that you can
mention, if you have specific client
interactions, quotes, like things like
that which you can mention in your post,
that is also going to make you stand out
because that's unique to you. You need
to remember, at the end of the day, we
are building a personal brand, and we
need to show people like what makes you
unique. It doesn't necessarily mean that
your service needs to be the newest
thing in the world, but it's just the
positioning and you and your service and
your clients and their situations, those
are the drivers for the unique
mechanism. Now, this is just going to
build insane authority, right? And
authority makes people listen to you,
and it eventually builds enough trust
where they'll buy from you. Very, very
simple. Key metrics that I would track
for these types of posts is going to be
saves and comments. Like, I think you'll
also see on LinkedIn as like a
insightful. So, there's like different
types of likes on LinkedIn. I wouldn't
usually look at it too much, but if you
see a lot of insightful likes on
LinkedIn, it usually means that it was a
specifically like very, very valuable
post. Format number four is going to be
the mechanism comparison post. So,
everyone who's selling a B2B service has
different options, right? Somebody
decides to pay an agency or do they
decide to do it in-house? Somebody
decides to pay for a software or do they
decide to vibe code it in-house, right?
Or do they decide to use a competing
software? So, you need to
explain to people why you guys are
better than the other options. So, this
is for people who are already a bit more
familiar with your content, they're
already a bit more familiar with the
mechanism, but we need to explain to
them that we are the best option out of
all the other options, right? But, this
is just the mechanism fundamentally. I'm
not I'm about your service specifically.
So, for example, for me, I'm selling
LinkedIn inbound, right?
LinkedIn inbound is way stronger than
cold email because cold email is a
short-term game where reply rates are
dropping every single month, and every
single month you need to send more
emails to get more customers. Whereas
Whereas LinkedIn inbound keeps
compounding, it brings leads to your
door, and people are actually happy to
work with you and willing to pay you
more money than any cold lead ever
would.
If I wanted to compare LinkedIn LinkedIn
inbound to something like ads, the truth
is just like the cost of a qualified
lead is way higher on something like
Google Ads. Or the fact that one
platform might take longer to see
results, right? Or the fact that one
platform might take more time. So,
there's all these benefits of all the
all these different things, and you I
would recommend mapping it out. If you
can use specific client examples of
saying, "This guy used to do this
channel or used to work with this uh
strategy, and now he's switched to us,
and now it's working." That's extremely
strong because it's immediately going to
mean that people are going to ignore the
original option, or people that are in
his previous situation are going to be
like, "Okay, let me take the same step
as him, and let me start working with
you." Or at least, you know, start be
more convinced about the mechanism that
we're selling. As an example, every
other channel costs more while
delivering less. Like LinkedIn organic
is by far the most untapped B2B channel
right now, no doubt. Um asset versus
rent. As I told you before, LinkedIn is
compounding, whereas other channels are
depreciating, and they are not built for
long-term growth.
Uh network growth. So, you're actually
going to build your personal brand. And
then value and impact. This type of post
with like channel comparisons, like
people are going to feel like you're
saving them time and money, which is
true. Like you are going to be saving
them time and money. Like your service
should be amazing. And it should drive
an ROI, and it should be better than all
these other channels. Like, that's a
given. So, we need to do a service to
the market by letting them know, right?
And the market, if you truly do this in
an authentic way, the market's going to
trust you, and they're going to see that
this guy's actually saving me time from
wasting time, wasting money on other
channels,
and he's just laying out the option for
me. And obviously, I could work with
them. I could also do it myself, right?
And then, there's that whole thing, and
a percentage of people will become
buyers.
Format five is the internal
milestone/personal
post. So, I wasn't a fan of personal
post for a very, very, very long time.
That being said, I kind of realized that
if you do it in the right way, it is
extremely strong. Because we don't want
to say, "Oh, I have a personal post
where Oh, this client just charged back,
and now, you know, because we didn't
deliver results, right?" Like, that's
like a horrible personal post to make.
Like, you don't want to ruin your
authority. But, if you think of it in a
way where you can subtly drop in little
lines and little milestones.
So, for example, one of my clients, Goji
Berry, they did a post about hitting X
number of ARR, and we just positioned it
as a personal post. And we were just
like, "Hey, look. We hit this much ARR.
This is everything we did so far. This
is, you know, our journey from zero."
And like, that builds a ton of trust,
because people see them in that
situation along the way.
And not only does it build like this
trust outside of just like a company in
the business space, like it builds that
personal trust, but it still keeps them
on authority, because they're hitting
milestones, right? They're achieving
their goals. They're getting that
dopamine. And that's really going to
resonate with anyone that's struggling
to hit revenue targets, that's
struggling to get leads. So, the
engagement driver, I would say this is
one of those posts where also like
comments and DMs are going to be huge.
Like, you'll tend to get a lot of a new
a lot of people which are like, "Okay,
this guy's super legit." And they'll
connect with you, they'll DM you,
they'll view your profile. And there'll
also be a lot of like conversation in
the comments, right? Um as I said,
though, like these do need to be real
and they need to be high specificity,
right? Like there needs to be exact
numbers that you can share or at least
something like, you know, a general
figure, right? Like we just hit six our
first six-figure month, right? Something
like that, for example, could work as
well. Friction in the selling is the
fact that, as I said before, it's an
authority post, this guy's a personal
post. So, it works extremely well. Key
metrics, we already talked about this.
So, format choice is only 50% of the
success. However, the remaining 50% is
going to depend on the posting structure
and the execution layout. Let me explain
you the algorithm a little bit. So, the
algorithm on LinkedIn now is very much
focused on pushing your content to the
right people, not necessarily a broad
amount of people. I mean, obviously, a
broad amount of the right people would
be ideal, but at the very least, the
right people, okay? Because that's what
that matters at the end of the day.
Like, if the people that are reading
your content are never going to like
benefit you, if it's just doesn't align
with your goal, there's no point. So,
what I would recommend is that you have
a very specific profile, and this is
where the profile is actually relevant
to the content, not just conversions,
but having a profile which is very
targeted to an ICP is going to help the
LinkedIn algorithm know who to push your
content out to, okay? And that's also
things that you should subtly mention in
your post is like the industries that
you work with, like the revenue levels,
like all of this stuff, it will
indirectly help the algorithm push it to
the right people.
The other thing is consistency over
frequency. So, if you truly cannot post
once a day at the same time every single
day, which by the way, is kind of the
bare minimum and you should be doing
that, um, the biggest thing is the
algorithm gets used to your content and
it will start expecting your content.
And when it doesn't get your content,
it's probably going to reduce the
performance and you're going to lose a
bit of momentum. Whereas, if you post
every single day at 8:00 a.m., you're
going to get yourself into the
algorithm, and then also your audience
is simply going to build the habit of
like, "Oh, let me see what this guy
posted about today. Oh, like the I
haven't seen this guy's post in the feed
today." They're going to be confused,
right? And somebody else is going to
take your spot in the feed, and then who
knows, imagine that's a competitor, and
then now they've taken your client,
right? So, posting at the same time is
actually much more important than you
think. And then I would do a very, very
minimum of five posts a week, but I like
to hold myself to a high standard. If
I'm not doing one post a day, then I've
failed that week. It's It's as simple as
that, okay?
And especially because Sunday is one of
the highest performing days, some days
perform a bit worse, it's still an
audience that you're attracting. Like,
it doesn't need to perform your as your
best day. And also, just make the
content a 10% better to make up for it.
Like, come on, guys, it's not that hard.
Now, the penalty for inconsistency is
the fact that if you don't miss your
schedule, you will build momentum, and
it will compound, trust me. Like, over
This is something which is a bit more
long-term, like I would say 3 to 6
months, but over 3 to 6 months, it will
really, really compound, because then in
the first hour of your post, you're
going to get such a huge amount of
engagement from people that expect it,
from the right people that see your
content, that all of your posts are
going to perform well. Like, literally.
Now, what is the content mix, okay? So,
using kind of the format above, what is
the mix? So, I would say we want to do
two proprietary insight
educational posts a week, okay? This is
those bottom-of-funnel style content,
um teaching people how to achieve the
outcome, cementing yourself as somebody
who knows what they're talking about.
Number one, one big name tag post, which
is top of funnel, okay? This is more
newsjacking or trendjacking, I would
call it. We will then do one mechanism
comparison post. This is in between, I
would say, bottom of funnel and middle
of funnel, where we kind of There's
people who are already aware of the
mechanism, but maybe they're considering
different options, and we want to cement
them into the belief that our mechanism
is the superior one.
Number The next one will be the personal
posts. So, this is, again, top of
funnel. So, this is where we're subtly
building authority and trying to build a
connection outside of just business,
because that's actually going to set you
apart from all the other competitors.
And then the next two are going to be
lead magnets. Right, lead magnets,
they're kind of a bit of They You can
position them how you want. You could do
a case study lead magnet, and then you
could do a very top of funnel cold lead
magnet. That's what I would recommend.
Case study lead magnets are by far the
highest converting type of post on
LinkedIn as a whole, like booking calls,
getting clients. And I've got a video
about that coming up, so you're going to
need to stay tuned for that one. That
being said, the other one you should do
should be as broad as possible, as
valuable as possible, just trying to get
as many eyeballs as possible, leveraging
trends, going into AI, making it like
the the craziest thing they've ever
seen. Now, the weekly rhythm, as I said
before, seven posts a week, don't miss
Sundays, don't miss Mondays. Um usually
in the middle of the week it might be a
little lower, but again, post every day
if you can, please. And the lead capture
layer is extremely interesting. And this
is because
I see a lot of people that think all the
work is done once they once they post,
once they click post. And the truth is,
unfortunately, that is not the case. So,
what do we do with the lead capture
layer? So, with the lead capture layer,
you want to essentially So, when
somebody comments to keyword, they will
either send you a connection request,
and what you need to do is you need to
set up a tool called Lead Shark. And
what that will do is either it will
auto-accept their connection, or it will
auto-connect with them because they've
commented that keyword.
They will then see every future post,
but also we're going to send them that
resource link that they've requested of
the lead magnet. That resource link is
going to be gated by an email opt-in
page, and this is how people get
hundreds of subscribers a day. And
you're basically just going to say,
"Hey, receive it instantly and a couple
bonuses if you opt in. You just need to
put your email and your name, and you're
going to get a ton more value as well."
Right? One good lead magnet can easily
add anywhere from 300 to 1,000 qualified
ICP connections and followers.
And you could easily be booking 5 to 10%
of these. Um obviously with 1,000 you
wouldn't book 10% of them, right? But
take 300, for example, like qualified
ICP connections. If you even book like
5%, that's like 15 calls from one post.
It's not unheard of.
And if you run DM follow-ups as well and
consistent emails, and also you keep
posting to keep them nurtured, like you
can imagine the amount of trust that
that builds. Now, just to explain why we
do comments and not links, the only time
I would do links if it was very bottom
of funnel and we just want to get direct
traffic. With comments we're actually
able to get this network where one
person comments and if they have a big
audience, their whole audience is going
to see it and then they comment and they
comment and they comment. And that's why
our lead magnets go so viral. And
especially if your competitors or
authorities in your space comment on
your post, people are going to see it
and they're going to be like, "These
guys are looking at this guy and seeing
what he has to say, so he must be legit,
right?" So it actually builds a lot of
trust. Um and actually positions you as
an even higher authority than those
other people, which is really strong. Um
so the next thing is, okay, when we add
in
all of these things, the formats, when
we have the structure, when we have the
capturing layer, all three of these
combined, at the end of the day what you
get out is going to be very high
impressions
and very high calls booked.
The truth is that month one was not 72
calls. I don't remember now. It It had
some calls booked, but it wasn't 72. But
it's the compounding of the system that
happened that allowed us to then book 72
calls in month three. Okay?
So, that being said, if you want us to
run this fully done for you, we are
taking on about five to six more clients
right now until I need to hire more
people to increase capacity. Apply to
work with me with the link in the
description. If you're not able to
afford a minimum of 3K a month, then we
will simply not be able to work
together. So, don't waste your time.
Um that being said, I'm really happy if
anybody did actually watch this fully to
the end. And the biggest thing here is
going to be taking action. So, whether
you need us to help you with that or
whether you can do that yourself, that's
amazing. Okay? And I will let you guys
take it from here.